<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<branchCategory xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><name>Combination Units</name><seoslug>Combination-Units~15652</seoslug><imageS>frl.combo.jpg</imageS><imageM>ACtypeB.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog></series_catalog><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;SMC&amp;apos;s air preparation (FRL) products offer a wide variety of filter, regulator, and lubricator units. Combination units include air filter regulator, air filter regulator mist separator, as well as ambient &amp;#xa0;dryers, booster regulators, precision regulators, mist separators, and a wide range of accessories. Obtain energy savings, with higher air flow rates and eight size options to ensure optimum performance for &amp;#xa0;every application. Cleaner environment with small Micron Filtration as standard to meet every application need. Reduced downtime with simple assembly and maintenance. Integrate electronic pressure switches, lock &amp;#xa0;out valves and &amp;quot;soft starts&amp;quot; for complete control over your pneumatic supply.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><breadCrumbs><breadCrumb><name>Airline Equipment</name><seoslug>Airline-Equipment</seoslug><id>15651</id></breadCrumb><breadCrumb><name>Combination Units</name><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><id>15652</id></breadCrumb></breadCrumbs><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction><branchItems><branchItem><id>87728</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AC-A</name><imageS>AC_A.jpg</imageS><imageM>AC_A.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>AC_A.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;P&amp;gt;SMC&amp;apos;S new AC-A series of modular type F.R.L. unit is available in five sizes and is interchangeable with the existing modular AC line. The pressure drop across the regulator has been reduced creating a more efficient unit with a maximum set pressure of 100 psi. The element and bowl on the AW and AF series is now one-piece, making element replacement easier. Required maintenance space has been reduced by as much as 46% on the AF series, depending on the body size. Bowls on the size 30 and 40 are now covered with a transparent bowl guard, completely protecting them from the environment, and making the interior contents visible from 360 degrees. The base color of the new AC-A series is urban white, maintaining a clean, modern look.&amp;lt;/P&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>128656</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AC-B</name><imageS>AC_A.jpg</imageS><imageM>AC_A.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>FRL_C.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;SMC&amp;apos;S new AC-B series of modular type F.R.L. unit is available in six basic sizes and is interchangeable with the existing modular AC line. The AC-B series has a maximum set pressure of 125 psi and offers embedded gauge and pressure switch options not found in the AC-A. The element and bowl on the AF series is now one-piece, making element replacement easier. Required maintenance space has been reduced by as much as 46% on the AFseries, depending on the body size. Bowls on size 30 and up are now covered with a transparent bowl guard, completely protecting them from the environment, and making the interior contents visible from 360 degrees. The base color of the new AC-B is urban white, maintaining a clean, modern look.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>87827</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AW-A</name><imageS>AW_A.jpg</imageS><imageM>AW_A.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>FRL_C.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;P&amp;gt;SMC&amp;apos;S series AW-A is a combination filter/regulator, minimizing space and piping by integrating two units into one. The pressure drop across the regulator section has been reduced creating a more efficient unit with a maximum set pressure of 100 psi. The element and bowl on the AW-A series is now one-piece, making element replacement easier. Bowls on the size 30 and 40 are covered with a transparent bowl guard, completely protecting them from the environment and making the interior contents visible from 360 degrees. This series is part of the family of modular air preparation units and can be combined with other similar sized products. The new AW-A is available in four body sizes with piping from M5 to 3/4&amp;quot; in Rc, NPT, and G thread types.&amp;lt;/P&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>128756</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AW-B</name><imageS>AW_A.jpg</imageS><imageM>AW_A.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>FRL_C.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>SMC&amp;apos;S series AW-B is a combination filter/regulator, minimizing space and piping by integrating two units into one. The AW-B series has a maximum set pressure of 125 psi and offers embedded gauge and pressure switch options not found in the AW-A while maintaining panel mounting interchangeability with the previous AW models. Bowls on the size 30 and up are covered with a transparent bowl guard, completely protecting them from the environment and making the interior contents visible from 360 degrees. This series is part of the family of SMC modular air preparation units and can be combined with other similar sized product. The new AW-B is available in four body sizes with piping from 1/8&amp;quot; to 1&amp;quot; in Rc, NPT and G thread types.</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>30795</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>ACG</name><imageS>3009B.jpg</imageS><imageM>3009B.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>ACG.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The&amp;#xa0;modular style ACG series allows you to pick a combination of air preparation equipment that best suit your particular application.&amp;#xa0; The selectable angle of the pressure gauge improves its&amp;apos; visibility, and the anti-revolving mechanism (PAT.PEND.) will not allow the pressure gauge to be revolved even after the handle is operated.&amp;#xa0; Assembly and maintenance are easily performed resulting in reduced downtime and labor savings.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>30801</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AWG</name><imageS>3025B.jpg</imageS><imageM>3025B.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>ACG.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A built-in pressure gauge, mountable at any angle, depending on the piping direction ensures good visibility of the pressure gauge, even when the AWG is mounted at an overhead or underfoot location. Equipped with a special mechanism, the pressure gauge will not be revolved even after the handle is operated. Due to the unique design, substantial space reduction is achieved when the AWG is panel mounted.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>15712</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AWD</name><imageS>awd.jpg</imageS><imageM>awd.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>AWD.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;P&amp;gt;For applications requiring micro-mist separation up to .01&amp;#xb5;m with adjustable pressure regulation, the AWD offers these features built into one unit. This combination of products saves space and mounting hardware. Available with ports from 1/8 to 1/2 with NPT, Rc and G (PF) threads as standard. The many options available such as auto-drain, gauge, variety of bowl choices and regulation set pressures make this series easy to configure to your application. &amp;lt;/P&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>15718</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AWM</name><imageS>awm.jpg</imageS><imageM>awm.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>AWD.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;
Combining a mist separator and regulator into one unit  simplifies piping and installation. This combination  controls the filtration to 0.3&amp;#xb5;m, for applications that  require cleaner air than regular filtration, such as  air blow off. As part of the family of modular air  preparation units, the AWM can be combined with other similar  sized products. This series is available with port sizes  from 1/8 to 1/2 with NPT, Rc or G threads. Many  standard options can also be ordered such as auto-drain,  gauges, etc.
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>15696</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AMR</name><imageS>3048.jpg</imageS><imageM>3048.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>AMR.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;
Series AMR is a combination regulator with mist separator.  The series offers high filtration (0.3&amp;#xb5;m) and a space savings, easy  piping design.  Options include auto drain and pressure switch.
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>15724</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>IW</name><imageS>4010.jpg</imageS><imageM>4010.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>IW.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;
Filter regulator series IW prevents moisture and dust in the compressed air line while maintaining pressure at a stable level, in spite of variations of both air consumption and air source pressure.
&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>15704</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AW - Special Environment</name><imageS>aw.jpg</imageS><imageM>aw.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>Epoxy.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This combination Filter/ Regulator minimizes space and piping by integrating the 2 units into one. Standard features include a relieving regulator, which can be quickly locked by pushing down on the adjustment knob. There are many options, which include gauges, auto-drain, metal bowl and covers, different set pressures, etc. The AW is part of the family of modular air preparation units and can be combined with other similar sized products. This series is available in four body sizes with piping from M5 to 3/4 in Rc, NPT or G thread types.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem><branchItem><id>15654</id><seoslug>Combination-Units</seoslug><type>FOLDER</type><name>AC - Special Environment</name><imageS>ac.jpg</imageS><imageM>ac.jpg</imageM><imageL></imageL><iso_symbol></iso_symbol><series_catalog>Epoxy.pdf</series_catalog><model></model><collateral></collateral><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><description>&amp;lt;P&amp;gt;The cost effective and clean looking AC series allows you to pick a combination of modular style air preparation equipment that best suits your needs. The series, available in 8 size options to ensure optimum performance, offers energy savings, with higher flow rates. Simple assembly and maintenance reduces downtime.&amp;#xa0; &amp;lt;FONT color=#ff0000&amp;gt;The current AC series is no longer being produced and is subject to available quantities only.&amp;#xa0; For size 10 models, please utilize the AC-A series.&amp;#xa0; For sizes 50~60, please utilize the AC-B series.&amp;#xa0; For sizes 20~40 please utilize the AC-A or AC-B series as appropriate to your performance and option needs.&amp;lt;/FONT&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/P&amp;gt;</description><bullets></bullets><preferredproduct>not-used-at-this-time</preferredproduct><removedproduct>unknown-content</removedproduct><hideFromProduction>0</hideFromProduction></branchItem></branchItems><configurableData><jsInitConfig></jsInitConfig><optionSelectHTML></optionSelectHTML><partNumberHTML></partNumberHTML><seriesName></seriesName><configuration_doc></configuration_doc><eds_file></eds_file><relatedProducts/></configurableData></branchCategory>
